The SCOAN Sunday Service
I'll bring my sin before the Blood of the Lamb
So that You can pray through me
I'll bring my guilt before the Lamb of God
Let's sing one more time.
I'll bring my sin before the Blood of the Lamb
So that You can pray through me
I'll bring my guilt before the Blood of the Lamb
I'll bring my sin before the Blood of the Lamb
So that You can pray through me
I'll bring all my guilt before the Lamb of God
So Spirit pray through me
Lift your hands and worship!
Say: "Spirit pray through me, Jesus!
I need your Spirit to pray!"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I'll bring my pain before the Blood of the Lamb
So that You can pray through me
I'll bring my shame before the Blood of the Lamb
I'll bring my pain before the Blood of the Lamb
So that You can pray through me
I'll bring my shame before the Blood of the Lamb
So Spirit pray through me
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Hallelujah!
I'll bring my grudge before the Blood of the Lamb
So that You can pray through me
I'll bring my grief before the Blood of the Lamb
I'll bring my grudge before the Blood of the Lamb
So that You can pray through me
I'll bring my grief before the Blood of the Lamb
I'll bring my grudge before the Blood of the Lamb
So that You can pray through me
Father, here I'm today bringing my grief before you Lord
Oh Lord
So that You can pray through me
So Spirit pray through me
Spirit pray through me
One more time say!
Come on bless the name of Jesus.
TT Monica Asefa
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 07/04/2019